

Nima Razi

BBA, Business Information Technology & Software Developer

🗹 nima.razi@hotmail.com 📞 (+358) 41 478 6217 🔮 65100 Vaasa, Finland

PROFILE

i've worked as software developer and in IT-support for over year. I've been involved in REST.API and ASP.NET projects varying from ERP's to web-development. I mainly focused on front-end and database-design both in studies and work.

WORK EXPERIENCE

05/2023 - 10/2023 | Software Developer, Cash-In Consulting Oy (ASP.NET, Oracle SQL & IT-support)

01/2022 - 08/2022 | Software Developer, Pilvilampi Software Oy (REST.API, SharePoint & Helpdesk)

06/2019 - 08/2019 | Cleaner, Kartanon Puhtauspalvelut Oy

05/2018 - 08/2018 | Cleaner, Kartanon Puhtauspalvelut Oy

10/2017 - 11/2017 | Greenhouse Worker, Wääksyn Puutarha Oy

06/2016 - 08/2016 | Newspaper Deliverer, Tampereen Ykkösjakelut Oy

LANGUAGES

finnish - excellent

english - excellent

farsi - good

swedish - weak

kurdish - weak

EDUCATION

08/2018 - 12/2022 | BBA, Business Information Technology, Vaasa University of Applied Sciences

08/2012 - 12/2016 | Matriculation Examination, Tampere High School of Technology

IT-EXPERIENCE

Microsoft 365: Word, PowerPoint, Excel, Access, SharePoint & Power BI 3ds Max, DaVinci Resolve, Oracle VM VirtualBox & Adobe XD WordPress & Piranha CMS Oracle SQL, MariaDB & Microsoft SQL Server

HTML, CSS & JavaScript (Bootstrap)

OTHER

B-drivers license Sports Scolarship & (B2) english | Tampere High School of Technology Consrciption Service, Pori Brigade 2017 LinkedIn (https://www.linkedin.com/in/nimarazi) GitHub (https://github.com/nima-razi)